## Hello, my name is CHRIS FELDMANN

and I'm a Digital Product Designer.

## **SPECIALTIES**

My specialization: I'm an interaction and creative generalist for digital, web and mobile technologies. I have a broad background that ranges from Fortune 500 companies, to an advertising company with national campaigns, as well as a fast-paced news environment. I use each experience as a building block, along with my passion for user-centered design thinking and learning to produce interactive and physical services.

**Expert level**: Adobe Creative Suite (including XD) **Advanced level**: HTML/CSS, Axure, Balsamiq, UXpin, user experience activities (wireframes, storyboards, usability testing, journey maps, etc.), Final Cut Pro, Pixologic ZBrush, Blender, Autodesk 3ds Max and Autodesk Sketchbook Pro **Working knowledge**: Javascript, Omniture, Adobe Analytics

## **EXPERIENCE**

The Courier-Journal | Digital Product Designer | October 2012 - Present

As a Product Designer I work at every phase of the digital product life-cycle for our online interactive content. I used UX/Service Design activities/strategies to redefine our newsroom workflow to reduce friction points for reporters/editors. I also create digital assets for interactive content, as well as graphic/animated digital content for online using my motion graphics, animation and graphic design skill sets.

My work has been recognized twice in the "Best of Gannett" competitions for interactive and animated editorial content. I also placed Third in a competition held by the Kentucky Press Association (KPA) for animated content.

PriceWeber | Digital Designer | January 2011 - October 2012

I utilized the entire Adobe Creative Suite, Autodesk 3ds Max, and Apple Final Cut Pro to develop exciting 2d/3d animation, stills, motion graphics, web design, audio production and video editing for promotional materials, presentations, and interactive content. **Clients include:** Hershey's, Cummins, Arvin Meritor, Valvoline, Carr, Riggs & Ingram (CPAs and Advisors), Early Times, and Brown-Forman Beverages

**U. of Cincinnati (DAAP)** | *Motion Design Instructor* | August 2010 - December 2010 Adjunct Instructor for the University of Cincinnati's College of Design, Architecture, Art and Planning. Teaching Motion Design with emphasis on user/audience experience

UC Simulation Center | Digital Designer | March 2009 - October 2010

Worked for Procter and Gamble (P&G) creating high performance modeling and visualization products (intended for consumer analysis/testing) for several **P&G brands including:** Tide, Pantene, Olay, Covergirl, Bounce, Sinex, Vicks, and Glad. Keeping in mind human factors and usability, I used Autodesk Inventor 2011, 3ds Max 2011, Mudbox 2011 and the Adobe Creative Suite to bring to life upstream P&G products with 2d/3d visualization, animation and still images.

Kinetic Vision | Digital Designer (Co-Op) | March 2008 - September 2008

Created 3d visualization products for various clients. **Clients include:** Oral B, Crest, Ethicon, Router Boss and Puget Sound Energy. Used Autodesk 3ds Max and the Adobe Creative Suite to provide high end product visualizations. Pioneered Kinetic Vision's workflow to include digital interactivity embedded within physical products.

Macy's, Inc. | Digital Designer (Co-Op) | March 2007 - September 2007

Created 3d visualization products for the Macy's national design standards redesign. I used Autocad and Autodesk 3ds Max to create 3d models of store fixtures and products for design visualizations, as well as Adobe Photoshop and Illustrator to create graphics and brands that aligned with Macy's design standards.

**EDUCATION** 

**University of Cincinnati** | College of Design, Architecture, Art and Planning (DAAP)

Degree Earned: Bachelor's of Science in Design

Dean's List student. Graduated with a GPA of 3.279.